# YOSSI KARASIK

# FULLSTACK | FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Checkout my portfolio https://www.YossiKarasik.com

# 052-8666064 yosikari@gmail.com www.github.com/yosikari www.linkedin.com/in/yosikari

# **ABOUT ME**

As a practical electrical engineer with 8 years of experience, I discovered my passion for programming while working with programmable controllers. I recently completed a 640-hour full-stack boot camp at Coding Academy, where I gained expertise in both front-end and back-end development. I continue to self-learn and build projects to expand my skills. As a highly motivated and collaborative team player, I'm now seeking a fullstack position where I can apply my expertise and make valuable contributions to the team.

#### **EDUCATION**

Secondary Atuda -Coding education **Electricity** Academy

Electricity 9 points. Practical Engineer. Full-stack bootcamp.

2012 - 2014 2022-2023 2000 - 2012

#### **EXPERTISE**

JavaScript | TypeScript | Html | CSS | SCSS React | Vue | Angular | Node.js | Express Socket.io | Redux | Vuex | NgRx | Firebase MongoDB | MySQL | Electricity and PLC

## MAIN PROJECTS

# Anyday (Monday clone)

2023

This project is a "pixel perfect" clone of 'monday.com' app. It was written using Node.js and MongoDB for the backend, and React in the frontend. This project contains the following features: a full login/signup including using FB, completely interactive boards, different board views, activity logs, charts, voice control, and more. I addition I used organized SCSS to make this app responsive to any device.

Repository: https://github.com/yosikari/Anyday Demo: https://anyday-za1z.onrender.com/

# Nextflix (Netflix clone)

2023

Was written using Typescript, Next.js, React custom hooks, Firebase (DB, Payment (Stripe), users service), and Tailwind, This app allows users to sign in via email or with Google/FB account and includes the following features: selecting a billing plan, watch trailers of the recent movies in Netflix (using an API), read movies description, add movies to watchlist and more...

Repository: https://github.com/yosikari/NextFlix Demo: https://next-flix-ebon.vercel.app/

#### Airbmb (Airbnb clone)

2023

Built with Prisma, MongoDB, Next.js, and Tailwind CSS, this Airbnb clone uses custom and built-in React hooks, including a dynamic modal component that's reused for filtering, login, and listing. The app is fully responsive, with Google/Github login, filters, and map integration. Users can view and post guesthouses for rental, powered by Cloudinary for image hosting.

Repository: https://github.com/yosikari/Airbmb Demo: https://airbmb-yosikari.vercel.app/

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Regional manager

Zohar Dalia Professional L.T.D

#### 2018-2022

Manager of the southern region at a chemical company. Responsible for over 150 company customers, managing sales and service providers. Examining supplementary equipment (dosing systems) in the field and providing a response in real time.

#### Mechanical electrician

Feldman ice-creams L.T.D

#### 2016 - 2018

Maintenance electrician, responsible for the integrity of a production line in a food factory. Installs and repairs electrical apparatus and electronic components of machinery and equipment. Writing programs for Siemens and Unitronics controllers and implementing them in the machines.

#### Electrician

Yehuda steel L.T.D 2014-2016

Maintenance electrician, responsible for the integrity of a production line in a steel factory.

Languages: Hebrew: Fluent | English: Fluent | Russian: Very good